<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Atmosphere Pro on </title>
    <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/contribute/atmosphere-pro/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Atmosphere Pro on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://dev3.atsign.wtf/contribute/atmosphere-pro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Following the Contrbuting Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/contribute/atmosphere-pro/3-contribution-guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/contribute/atmosphere-pro/3-contribution-guidelines/</guid>
      <description>Here at Atsign, we LOVE pull requests. You may have been part of various teams &amp;amp; projects where they followed different styles of contributing to GitHub repositories (squash &amp;amp; rebase, or committing to the same branch,..). But here at Atsign, all of our projects, apps, and services are open-sourced and the fork and pull request process seems to work the best for us.
See the CONTRIBUTING.md file in the root of the repository to see how we want you to set up your repository when making contributions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forking the Repository</title>
      <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/contribute/atmosphere-pro/2-git-clone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/contribute/atmosphere-pro/2-git-clone/</guid>
      <description>Now, it is time to fork the atmospher
  Make sure you are logged into GitHub
  Head over to atmosphere_pro and click &amp;ldquo;Fork&amp;rdquo;.
  You should be given prompted to create a new repository on your account. Change these settings to your needs. Change the repository name, description, or copy all of the branches if you&amp;rsquo;d like. We recommend the default settings.  Now that you have the repository on your own personal GitHub account, you can get the GitHub url by clicking on &amp;ldquo;Code,&amp;rdquo; clicking &amp;ldquo;HTTPS,&amp;rdquo; then copy the url.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/contribute/atmosphere-pro/1-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/contribute/atmosphere-pro/1-introduction/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, we will be cloning our project so that you can make contributions to our end-to-end encrypted file transfer app, atmosphere pro. To get started, you will need the following:
 Git A GitHub account A code editor like VSCode for coding in Dart/Flutter. The Flutter framework An environment to test and run the application (Android, iOS, macOS, or Windows).  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making Contributions</title>
      <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/contribute/atmosphere-pro/4-making-contributions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/contribute/atmosphere-pro/4-making-contributions/</guid>
      <description>Now that you have your fork all setup and you&amp;rsquo;ve appropriately setup your repository to be following the Contributing Standards, it&amp;rsquo;s time to get to the fun part- coding!
 Fetch the latest changes from the upstream repository.  git fetch upstream Reset your fork&amp;rsquo;s trunk to be exactly as the upstream trunk branch. IMPORTANT: Do this only at the beginning when you begin working on your contribution. It will overwrite and delete and local changes you&amp;rsquo;ve made and make it exactly as the code we have it in the upstream trunk branch.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
