<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Get Started on </title>
    <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/start/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Get Started on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/start/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Flutter Development</title>
      <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/start/flutter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/start/flutter/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java Development</title>
      <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/start/java/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/start/java/</guid>
      <description>Setting Up Your Development Environment # Install Java  The first step in getting your developer environment ready, is to install Java 8 or higher on your local machine.
Install Maven  Next step is to install maven and add it to your PATH. Maven is a great tool for managing Java projects and will be useful for development atPlatform applications.
Clone the Java Client  Fork our at_java repository Create a new directory on your local machine where you want the java client source code to live.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT Devices</title>
      <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/start/iot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/start/iot/</guid>
      <description>Introduction #Here at Atsign, we believe in a world where IoT devices have atSigns and send their data end-to-end-encrypted to other atSigns. We&amp;rsquo;d love to work with you on adding security to your IoT devices. Please contact us at info@atsign.com or join our discord and ask us about anything and we will be happy to answer!
Ssh! No Ports #Want to ssh to your remove device without any open ports?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Other</title>
      <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/start/other/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/start/other/</guid>
      <description>Open Source Contributions #We LOVE open source. Any and all contributions are welcome.
The atPlatform consists of many open-sourced GitHub repositories. To start, go into any repository and find the CONTRIBUTING.md file to see how you can properly setup your fork to make contributions to our projects. Here is an example of the contributing guidelines for making contributions to the dev site that you are reading now. There may be different contributing guidelines for each repository, so be sure to read the CONTRIBUTING.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
