<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Get Started on </title>
    <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/start/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Get Started on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://dev3.atsign.wtf/start/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Flutter</title>
      <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/start/flutter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/start/flutter/</guid>
      <description>Setting Up Your Development Environment #1. Get an editor for programming in Dart #Some editors we recommend:
 Visual Studio Code Android Studio  2. Install Flutter/Dart on your machine #See Flutter&amp;rsquo;s instructions on getting the Flutter environment setup:
 Install Flutter on MacOS Install Flutter on Windows Install Flutter on Linux  3. Install at_app #at_app is a command-line tool for quickly creating atPlatform apps. It is similar to flutter create but adds atPlatform capabilities to your flutter apps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java</title>
      <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/start/java/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/start/java/</guid>
      <description>Setting Up Your Development Environment # Install Java  The first step in getting your developer environment ready, is to install Java 8 or higher on your local machine.
Install Maven  Next step is to install maven and add it to your PATH. Maven is a great tool for managing Java projects and will be useful for development atPlatform applications.
Clone the Java Client  Fork our at_java repository Create a new directory on your local machine where you want the java client source code to live.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT Devices</title>
      <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/start/iot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/start/iot/</guid>
      <description>What is IoT? #IoT–Internet of Things–is a system of interconnecting devices, mechanical or electronic, that are designed to work together to provide a service, such as the transmission of information, or the control of a device.
In simple terms, an IoT device is any device (such as a camera, a smart phone, a thermostat, a TV, a computer, etc) that is connected to the internet. IoT devices have sensors that are always collecting data and sending it through the Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Other</title>
      <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/start/other/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/start/other/</guid>
      <description>Open Source Contributions #We LOVE open source. Any and all contributions are welcome.
The atPlatform consists of many open-sourced GitHub repositories. To start, go into any repository and find the CONTRIBUTING.md file to see how you can properly setup your fork to make contributions to our projects. Here is an example of the contributing guidelines for making contributions to the dev site that you are reading now. There may be different contributing guidelines for each repository, so be sure to read the CONTRIBUTING.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
