<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Setup dess on AWS on </title>
    <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/tutorials/dess/aws/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Setup dess on AWS on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://dev3.atsign.wtf/tutorials/dess/aws/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Activation of atSign</title>
      <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/tutorials/dess/aws/7-activation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/tutorials/dess/aws/7-activation/</guid>
      <description>Next up we need to activate it
Login to your dashboard at atsign.com/dashboard
Open “my atSigns”
Open “managed” of atSign you are registering”
Navigate to Advance settings:
If you have already activated your atSign you will be prompted to erase all your data first
Once done you are able to link your atSign with your private dess. Use your domain and port number with which you have created service on your cloud instance and press Activate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instance setup and dess deployment</title>
      <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/tutorials/dess/aws/5-setup-and-deployment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/tutorials/dess/aws/5-setup-and-deployment/</guid>
      <description>Open your LightSail console
By now you should see your instance in “Running state”
Open it and on tab Connect click on “Connect using SSH”
You should be presented by a new window with command line:
Before we do anything else, we should update the system:
sudo apt update &amp;amp;&amp;amp; sudo apt upgrade This might take some time, but it will make sure we have latest repository information and the system is up to date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/tutorials/dess/aws/1-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/tutorials/dess/aws/1-introduction/</guid>
      <description>In this step-by-step guide I will walk you through all steps required to setup your own private dess (distributed edge secondary server) using AWS (Amazon Web Services). Please use the index to skip some steps in case you have already completed them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pre-requisites</title>
      <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/tutorials/dess/aws/2-prerequisites/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/tutorials/dess/aws/2-prerequisites/</guid>
      <description>Registered atSign(s) to setup An AWS account A Fully Qualified Domain Name (FQDN)  1. Registering your atSign #This topic is already well documented. Please follow the guidance of Our FAQs and register via the registrar site.
2. Sign-up for AWS account #If you are new to AWS, signing up for an account is free! The cost of running dess is about 10$/month. You can create your account at Amazon Web Services and as of June 6th, 2021 there is a “free tier” available which was used during the making of this guide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing AWS Instance</title>
      <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/tutorials/dess/aws/3-prep-aws-instance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/tutorials/dess/aws/3-prep-aws-instance/</guid>
      <description>Now since I am new to AWS, the easiest way to get started is by using the LightSail service from service catalog. This will enable you to deploy small system which is more then capable of handling dess at pre-set price.
Welcome to LightSail:
First step is to create new instance. Fortunately, we have big orange button that can do just that!
There are several options we are presented at this moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing your instance for network access</title>
      <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/tutorials/dess/aws/4-prep-network-access/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/tutorials/dess/aws/4-prep-network-access/</guid>
      <description>Assignment of Static IP #Next up, is to provide our instance with a static IP and linking our domain to it.
When you click on your instance name, it will take you to the management console, which should look like this:
This is where you control hardware, connectivity and if needed can delete your instance.
Lets configure a static IP address for your new instance. Navigate to Networking and click on Create static IP:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Registration of atSign in your private dess</title>
      <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/tutorials/dess/aws/6-registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/tutorials/dess/aws/6-registration/</guid>
      <description>At this step you should already have your atSign registered at atsign.com. If not go do it!
I have registered my own free atSign (@44likelycanary) which I will link to my dess.
In your instance console, navigate to dess folder. If you were following this guide it will be located in:
We now need to create the service that will host our atSign by executing the dess-create command:
$ sudo dess-create @44likelycanary 4atsign.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
