<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reference on </title>
    <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/reference/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reference on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>@sign</title>
      <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/reference/atsign/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/reference/atsign/</guid>
      <description>What is an @sign #An @sign is a handle (e.g. @alice) that functions as your digital identity. It uses end-to-end encryption to ensure that your data is 100% owned and controlled by you.
An @sign has two states: deactivated and activated. To activate an @sign, CRAM authenticate into your secondary server. After successful CRAM authentication, your @sign is activated where a PKAM key pair is generated by your device and the CRAM key will be invalid; so that only you own the keys to your secondary server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pricing / Costs</title>
      <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/reference/pricing-and-costs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/reference/pricing-and-costs/</guid>
      <description>Since the @platform is fully open sourced and everyone can contribute, there is no cost for developers! When you make an app on the @platform, people that use your apps will not have to pay any fees for infrastructure or storage! The way that AtSign generates revenue is by using our special identifier which is known as an @sign. An @sign can come in many flavors with corresponding prices ranging from free, $10, $100, $1000, $5000.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Encryption</title>
      <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/reference/encryption/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/reference/encryption/</guid>
      <description>Definition #Encryption is a means of achieving privacy. It is a part of cryptography which has the Greek origin meaning of &amp;ldquo;secret writing&amp;rdquo;. The goal of encryption is that assuming that an unwanted third party is eavesdropping on an insecure channel, said person would not be able to comprehend the transmitted information. Decryption is the process of converted encrypted information into a comprehensible format. Encryption and Decryption algorithms are known as ciphers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy</title>
      <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/reference/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/reference/privacy/</guid>
      <description>We live in an age of information. Information is an asset that has a similar value much like other assets that you might own. As an asset, that information must be secured from potential attacks or unauthorized access. There are several security goals that must be considered:
 Confidentiality: Hidden from unauthorized access. Integrity: Protected from unauthorized change. Availability: Available to an authorized party when needed. Authentication/Liveness: Ensuring the session is &amp;ldquo;current&amp;rdquo; rather than a replay of an earlier session.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Polymorphism</title>
      <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/reference/polymorphism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/reference/polymorphism/</guid>
      <description>Definition #The condition of occuring in several different forms.
Polymorphism on the @platform is the ability to share different data depending on the context of who’s asking. @platform applications enable you to setup multiple personas for different areas of your life. When you share data with someone else, the value of that data may be different depending on the person receiving that data. This is true for both sides, you may ask for data from different sources and get a different answer for each one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public and Private Keys</title>
      <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/reference/public-private-keys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/reference/public-private-keys/</guid>
      <description>Definition #A private key is used in asymmetric key cryptography. Asymmetric key cryptography is based on applying mathematical functions to numbers to achieve personal secrecy. It uses two keys, one being the private key. If you think of decryption as locking and unlocking padlocks with keys, then the padlock that is locked with a public key can only be unlocked with its corresponding private key.
On the other hand, public keys are distributed to the trusted masses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self-Encryption Key</title>
      <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/reference/self-encryption-key/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/reference/self-encryption-key/</guid>
      <description>Definition #Self-Encryption key is an AES symmetric key that you own for encrypting data for yourself.
@platform #In the @platform, the self-encryption key is used to encrypt data that is stored in your own secondary server. It is crucial that this key is kept secret and owned only by you so that third parties like Atsign cannot see your data.
The self-encryption key is generated during the CRAM process when your PKAM RSA keypair is generated and your @sign is activated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRAM</title>
      <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/reference/cram/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/reference/cram/</guid>
      <description>Definition #CRAM is a term you may have heard of when reading about the @platform. CRAM stands for challenge response authentication mechanism. It is an algorithm/mechanism used in cryptography commonly used for authentication in protocols.
@platform #You use your CRAM secret to activate your @ sign and authenticate into your (secondary server)[/docs/atplatform/secondary-server] secondary server for the first time. Once authenticated, you may add, update, delete, and lookup keys in your own secondary server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PKAM</title>
      <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/reference/pkam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/reference/pkam/</guid>
      <description>Definition #PKAM stands for public key authentication mechanism. It is a mechanism for encrypting/decrypting data between two parties.
@platform #The @platform&amp;rsquo;s packages and SDKs help apps generate a RSA PKAM public/private keypair and save this in a .atKeys file containing these keys. Since Atsign provided the CRAM secret, this poses an vulnerability since this is a shared secret between you and Atsign. To avert this, a new RSA PKAM keypair is generated on your device and the CRAM secret is no longer valid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Namespace</title>
      <link>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/reference/namespace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev3.atsign.wtf/docs/reference/namespace/</guid>
      <description>Definition #AtSign&amp;rsquo;s CTO, Colin Constable says this in an interview on Namespaces: &amp;ldquo;Most people are familiar with DNS (domain name system): for example, if you type “cnn.com”, “fox.com”, or “bbc.com”, you get news sites. But you can’t just type in “news” and expect the Internet to tell you which particular flavor of news you want. We need to create namespaces so that humans can remember the name and computers can translate it to Internet protocol.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
